Email: liliwfxa@gmail.com Mobile: +1-817-734-9751 Portfolio LinkedIn

SUMMARY

With a 12-year track record in e-commerce and real estate analytics, I've driven a startup to reach \$5 million in sales and pioneered a comprehensive five-dimensional real estate product strength metric system. Currently, I am advancing my data expertise at the UW's Master of Information Systems, further honing my skills in data analysis, reporting, and predictive modeling to further impact business strategies and decision-making.

EDUCATION

University of Washington - Michael G. Foster School of Business

Seattle, WA

Master of Science in Information Systems

June 2024 (expected)

Hunan University of Arts and Science

Hunan, China

Bachelor of Science in marketing; GPA: 3.83/4.00

September 2010

SKILL

- Programming: SQL, Python, R
- Data Visualization: Excel, Tableau, Power BI, Microsoft PowerPoint Programming libraries (Matplotlib, etc)
- Modeling: Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, K-means Clustering, Hierarchical Clustering
- Certification: Google Data Analytics
- Strategic Analytical Skills: Critical Thinking, Problem-solving, Statistical Analysis

PROJECTS

Pizza Sales KPI Report

• Executed SQL queries to extract key performance indicators for pizza sales and developed intuitive Tableau dashboard to depict sales trends, effectively communicating business insights.

Call Center Service Analysis

• Employed SQL to capture and analyze call volume, service quality, and customer sentiment; designed a PowerBI dashboard to visualize the trends, providing a strategic platform for enhancing customer service.

Alibaba User Behavior

• Utilized Pandas, Seaborn for data analysis to uncover user behavior trends, and applied K-means clustering in machine learning for customer RFM segmentation, guiding targeted marketing strategies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Founder and Owner

Changsha, China

ATMT: Start-up E-commerce Specialized in Cosmetics

2016 - 2022

- Revenue Achievement: Achieved a 30% increase in web traffic and \$5 million sales through strategic A/B testing, targeted SEO, and incisive market analysis to optimize product lines and marketing.
- Campaign Success: Launched a \$12K referral drive, expanding membership by 150%.
- **Team Leadership:** Fostered a '5Es' team culture, leading a compact team to innovate and implement dynamic e-commerce strategies.

Marketing Analyst

Changsha, China

Shenzhen World union Consultancy: Top 10 Chinese Real Estate Consulting Firms

2013 - 2016

- Sales Growth: Enhanced sales by 10% over three quarters through monitoring and analysis of market indicators like transaction volume and sales revenue.
- **Product Metrics:** Developed a five-dimensional real estate product strength metric system (encompassing brand, location, product, amenities, and pricing), improving product sales velocity by 12%.
- Data Insights: Designed key performance indicator reports and dashboards, aiding shareholders in data-driven decision-making.

Senior Sales Manager

Changsha, China

Shenzhen World union Consultancy: Top 10 Chinese Real Estate Consulting Firms

2010 - 2013

- Sales Champion: Analyzed customer data to tailor sales approaches, leading to personal sales of \$10 million and earning the title of 'Annual Sales Champion' twice.
- **Team Leadership:** Established a performance framework and motivational policies, driving the team to a \$30 million sales achievement.